… for Android & iOS.

Privacy Policy for this website
===============================

Privacy Policy
==============

In this privacy policy we inform you about the processing of your personal data.

If you want to change your privacy settings (grant consent or revoke your previously granted consent), click [here](#) to change your settings.

Responsible
-----------

Karl Ulrich Gissel, Heidi Kraken, Klintstraße 13, 27619 Schiffdorf, Deutschland, [ved.k1730952259caskc1730952259ur@tc1730952259atnoc1730952259](mailto:contact@rucksack.dev),

Hosting
-------

### All-inkl.com

Our website is hosted by our processor [All-inkl.com](https://all-inkl.com/), ALL-INKL.COM – Neue Medien Münnich, René Münnich, Hauptstraße 68, 02742 Friedersdorf, Germany.

Connection data are processed to provide and to deliver the website. Data are not stored beyond access for the mere purpose of delivery and provision of the website.

The legal basis of processing is the legitimate interest (absolute technical necessity to provide and to deliver the “website” service which you have explicitly requested by visiting the website according to Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR combined with § 25 TTDSG.

Connection data and other personal data are also processed in connection with various other functions or services in order to operate the website. Detailed information is provided in this Data Privacy Statement and in the individual functions or services.

Server Log Files
----------------

Connection data are processed to monitor the technical function and to increase the reliability of our webhost. The duration of processing is limited to 365 days.

The legal basis of processing is the legitimate interest (absolute technical necessity of a server log file as fundamental data basis for failure analysis and for security measures in connection with the “website” service which you have explicitly requested by visiting the website) according to Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR combined with § 25 TTDSG.

Contact Form
------------

You can contact us by using a contact form provided on our website. After submission of the contact form, the controller will process the personal data you have provided for the purpose of handling your request on the basis of your consent which you have given by submitting the form according to Art. 6 (1) (a) GDPR, until revocation.  
You have no legal or contractual obligation to provide personal data. If you do not provide such data, you are simply not able to submit and we are not able to process your request.

Security Services
-----------------

On this website we use the offer of security service providers such as Captcha services to avoid non-human and automated input.

Analysis Services
-----------------

### Google Analytics

If you give your consent, we will process your personal data in cooperation with the service [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/), Google LLC, Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA, as joint controllers for the purpose of failure analysis and statistical analysis of our website. A failure to give consent will have no immediate impact on the function of the website, although a lack of statistic data will make it more difficult for us to sophisticate the website. You can revoke your consent by changing the settings at [Privacy settings](# "Datenschutzeinstellungen").

We will enable the service to collect connection data, data of your web browser and data of accessed content and to execute analysis software and to store data on your terminal device. The service anonymizes collected data immediately after such data were collected and provides us with statistics for analysis containing anonymous data. We use these statistics for failure analysis and for the sophistication of our website. Data on your terminal device are kept for up to two years.

The legal basis of processing is your consent according to Article 6 (1) (a) GDPR. The Google group transfers your personal data to the USA. The legal basis for data transfer to the USA is your consent in accordance with Art. 49 Para. 1 a in conjunction with Art. 6 Para. 1 a GDPR. Before you gave your consent, you were informed that the USA does not have a data protection level that complies with EU standards. In particular, US intelligence agencies can access your data without being informed about it and without you being able to take legal action against it. For this reason, the European Court of Justice ruled in a judgment that the previous adequacy decision (Privacy Shield) was invalid.

Right to object
---------------

You have the right to object to processing if your personal data is processed based on legitimate interests.

We will then cease the processing carried out on this basis, unless there are compelling and legitimate reasons for us to do so.

You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data for the purpose of direct marketing. In this case, we will cease the processing of your personal data for the purpose of direct mail.

The withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

Withdrawal
----------

You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time by changing the settings at [Privacy settings](# "Privacy settings").

If you have given your consent to receipt of advertising by email, you may withdraw your consent by clicking the unsubscribe link. In this case, we will cease the processing operations, unless there is any other legal basis.

The withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

Right to data subject
---------------------

You have the right to access to, rectification, erasure and restriction of processing of personal data.

You have also the right to data portability if the processing of your personal data is based on your consent or on a contract concluded with you.

You have also the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority. If you need more information on the supervisory authorities in the European Union, go to [here](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm "DPAs").

Other web projects

Proudly powered by [WordPress](https://wordpress.org/) | Theme: [Bulk](https://themes4wp.com/)

In case you want to change your privacy settings (e.g. issue consent or revoke an already issued consent) please click on the button below. [Settings](#)

 for Wordpress and WooCommerce.")

Data protection

Details

  English

Heidi Kraken, Owner: Karl Ulrich Gissel (Registered business address: Germany), would like to process personal data with external services. This is not necessary for using the website, but allows me to interact even more closely with them. If desired, please make a choice:

 for Wordpress and WooCommerce.")

Data protection

Details

  English

Heidi Kraken, Owner: Karl Ulrich Gissel (Registered business address: Germany), would like to process personal data with external services. This is not necessary for using the website, but allows me to interact even more closely with them. If desired, please make a choice:

Analysis / Statistics (1 Service)

Anonymous evaluation for troubleshooting and further development

* * *

Google Analytics

Google LLC, USA

Loading details

[Accept  
selection](#)

[Accept  
nothing](#)

[Accept  
all](#)
